What is the difference between a merge and a rebase?

Merging is simpler than rebasing. When merging, Git creates a new commit that combines the changes from both branches. This commit is different in that it is a merge commit, which shows when and where the merge occured.

Rebasing, while more difficult, it is a more advnaced and powerful technique than merging. When rebasing, Git replays the changes from the rebased branch which results in a linear history; as if the changes from the rebased branch were made directly on top of the base branch, without any merge commits.

What is a remote repository?

It is a repo that exists on a server or another location outside of a locale development environment. This allows users to collaborate and share code and updates between eachother.
